dealflicks.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Movie Ticket Deals, Discounts, Offers, & Coupons

At Dealflicks, we want to make your moviegoing experience better. As part of that effort, we want you to feel comfortable when you visit or use our Services (the websites and related mobile apps on which this Privacy Policy is displayed, and the services that we make available though those websites and apps). We also understand that you may have some important questions for us about what information we collect when you use our Service, why we collect that information, and how we may use and disclose it to others. We've created this Privacy Policy to help answer those questions. By using our Services, you are indicating to us that you agree to our collection, use and disclosure of your information, as described in this Privacy Policy. 

###  WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED? 

Here's what we collect from you when you use the Service: 

User-Provided Information: When you use the Service, and specifically when you do things like enter a search query, register for the Service, or create a user profile, you may be required to provide certain forms of information. For example, when you search for a movie in Los Angeles you would need to enter your movie choice and other information, like your neighborhood and date when you will see the show. When you register for the Service, we also ask you to provide an e-mail address and to select a password. You may also need to enter information that would be considered "personally identifiable" (that is, information that would allow us to directly identify you, such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, and telephone number). 

Third-Party Login Functionality: We allow users with accounts on third-party services, such as Facebook and Google, to log into the Service using functionality that those third parties provide (such as Facebook Connect and Google's OpenID-based authentication mechanism). By using this Facebook or Google functionality to log into the Service, you permit us to access and use specific identifying information related to your Facebook or Google account. While these services make a variety of information available, Dealflicks will associate only your e-mail address or other unique user account identifier with your Dealflicks account. 

We also allow you to integrate various functionalities from other services with Dealflicks. If you choose to take advantage of this integration feature, we will ask you for your login credentials for the other service. By providing those credentials, you are agreeing that we can access and store the information that the other service's functionality contains, including personally identifiable information. 

"Automatically Collected" Information: Like many websites and mobile apps, when you use the Service we may automatically record certain information about your visit from your web browser or our mobile app such as your IP address, the pages of the service you view, or details regarding the searches you run on the Service, such as what you are searching for, the date and time when you initiated a search, and the location from which you initiated the search. We collect and may use this information to understand and analyze the aggregate or "big picture" usage trends and preferences of our users. 

"Cookies" Information: One form of "automatically collected" information we record is information stored by "cookies." When you use the Service, we may send one or more cookies to your computer or your mobile device. We use both "session" and "persistent" cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track various types of information. A session cookie is one that disappears after you close your browser or our mobile app. While a persistent cookie remains after you close your browser or the mobile app (and may be used by your browser or the mobile app when you later return to the Service), persistent cookies generally can be removed. You can review the appropriate "Help" file in your Web browser or your mobile device to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. 

We use [Sense360](http://sense360.com/), a third party technology provider, to help us better understand how our users use Dealflicks and their devices. Dealflicks sends raw sensor data generated by your device to Sense360. This sensor data may include information from GPS receivers, accelerometers, gyroscopes, and other sensors, which may allow Sense360 to determine, for example, your device’s location, acceleration, and orientation. Sense360 may use this data to send us analytic reports regarding how our users are using Dealflicks and their devices, or for other purposes. To learn more, please visit Sense360’s privacy policy, available [here.](http://sense360.com/privacy-policy.html)

###  HOW IS THE INFORMATION USED? 

Dealflicks uses the information you provide or that we collect to keep this great thing going-- that is, to develop, operate, maintain, enhance, and provide the Service, to develop new products and services, and to customize and target content that may be more interesting, relevant or useful to you, including advertisements, and for other administrative purposes. 

Here are some examples of how we may use the information you provide or that we collect: 

We may use your email address to contact you for administrative purposes, including: 

We may use your email to give you updates on the Service's features and progress (such as new deal-search features or functions that we may add), and to provide you with promotional materials and offers (such as discounts on movies and concessions that may become available, or news about movies). Generally, you have the ability to opt-out of receiving emails about Service updates and promotional materials and offers, either through links provided in the email messages we send to you or by updating your account preferences through the Service. 

We may communicate with via email or another form of electronic notification regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Service. 

If you are logged into your account and using the Service, we may associate information regarding your usage of the Service with your account and with other information that we have collected about you, such as your search history. If you have not yet established an account with us (or you have not signed into the Service using a third-party login mechanism, described above), we record the searches you perform to a cookie. If that you later establish an account with us, or sign into our Service with that cookie still present on your computer, we may associate the searches recorded on that cookie with your new account. 

###  HOW IS THE INFORMATION SHARED OR DISCLOSED? 

We may provide personally identifiable information to third parties for their use in helping us perform our internal business functions. These are things like processing payments for us, or performing maintenance, security, data analysis, email transmission, or data hosting on our behalf. We will do our best to require these third parties to maintain your information securely, to not use it for purposes other than providing services to us, and to refrain from disclosing the information except when required by law. 

Dealflicks may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to: (1) satisfy legal obligations or comply with legal process (such as a subpoena) served on Dealflicks; (2) protect Dealflicks and others from fraudulent, abusive, predatory, or unlawful uses or activity; (3) investigate and defend Dealflicks against any legal claims or threats; (4) protect and defend the rights or property of Dealflicks; (5) take action on user complaints, or (6) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Dealflicks, the Service, or the public. 

If there is a change in ownership of Dealflicks, including through a merger with, acquisition by, or sale of assets to another entity, we may sell or otherwise transfer all information you provide to us, including personally identifiable information, to that entity. 

Dealflicks may disclose aggregated or other types of non-personally identifiable information, including "automatically collected" and "cookies" information that is non-personally identifiable, to third parties for various purposes. For example, Dealflicks may disclose non-personally identifiable information to interested third parties to assist them in understanding the usage, viewing, and demographic patterns on the Service, or to enhance your ability to conduct efficient and accurate searches. 

###  CHOICE. 

We think that you benefit from a more personalized experience when we know more about you and what you like. However, you can limit the information you provide to Dealflicks, and you can limit the communications that Dealflicks sends to you. 

You can manage your email and notice preferences by logging into your account through the Dealflicks website, entering the “My Account” section, and selecting “Email Subscriptions,” You can also manage your subscriptions by following subscription management instructions contained in the commercial e-mails that we send you. You may choose to subscribe to some types of messages, and may choose to unsubscribe from others. You may update your subscription preferences at any time. Please note that even if you unsubscribe from promotional email messages, we may still need to contact you with important transactional information related to your account and your purchases. For example, even if you have unsubscribed from our promotional email messages, we will still send you confirmations when you make purchases on the Site. 

You may manage how your browser handles Cookies by adjusting its privacy and security settings. Browsers are different, so refer to instructions related to your browser to learn about cookie-related and other privacy and security settings that may be available. You can opt-out of being targeted by certain Third-Party Ad-Servers online using the National Advertising Initiative’s Opt-Out Tool, or on TRUSTe’s site. 

You may manage how your mobile device and mobile browser share certain Device Data with Dealflicks, as well as how your mobile browser handles Cookies by adjusting the privacy and security settings on your mobile device. Please refer to instructions provided by your mobile service provider or the manufacturer of your device to learn how to adjust your settings. 

You may also manage the sharing of certain Personal Information with us when you connect with us through social networking platforms or applications. Please refer to the privacy policy and settings of the social networking website or application to determine how you may adjust our permissions and manage the interactivity between Dealflicks and your social networking account or your mobile device. 

If you wish to opt out of receiving offers directly from our Business Partners, you can follow the opt-out instructions in the emails that they send you. 

###  THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISERS AND ADVERTISING TECHNOLOGY PROVIDERS. 

Our advertising technology partners may use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements that appear on the Service. Our advertising technology partners automatically receive your IP address and other log file information when this happens. They may also use cookies to serve advertisements to you both on our Service and on other websites and services based on your visits to, and use of the Service, as well as based on your visits to third-party sites and services on the Internet (collectively, "Usage Information"). Our advertising technology partners also may, in accordance with their privacy policies, permit third parties to target advertisements that are displayed to you, both on and off the Service, based on your Usage Information. 

Aside from what is described above, we do not provide personal information to our advertising technology partners without your consent. 

###  LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SERVICES. 

Our Services may include links to third-party services. When you link to a third-party service, you should understand that our Privacy Policy no longer applies, and that the third-party's privacy practices may not be the same as ours. 

###  THE SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION. 

Dealflicks employs various physical, managerial, and technical safeguards that are designed to help protect the integrity and security of our systems and to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personally identifiable information that we control. For example, we scramble your password during transmission, and limit the employees who can access personally identifiable information to a small set who need such information to perform their jobs. We are not, however, in a position to guarantee the security of your information. 

If Dealflicks learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically, either by email on via our website, so that you can take appropriate protective steps. These methods of communicating with you are only examples. We retain the right to decide which method we will use to notify you of a security breach, and will do so consistent with our legal obligations. 

###  WHERE WE OPERATE 

Our servers and data centers are located in the United States. If you choose to use the Service from outside the U.S., then you should know that you are transferring your personally identifiable information outside of your region and into the U.S. for storage and processing. By providing your personally identifiable information to us through your use of the Service, you agree to that transfer, storage, and processing in the U.S. Also, we may transfer your data from the U.S. to other countries or regions in connection with storage and processing of data, fulfilling your requests, and operating the Service. You should know that each region can have its own privacy and data-security laws, some of which may be less stringent than your own region. 

###  HOW WILL YOU KNOW WHETHER DEALFLICKS' PRIVACY POLICY HAS CHANGED? 

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. If we substantially revise the policy (and we will use our discretion to determine if the revision is substantial) we may send e-mails to our registered users containing a link to the updated policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time to stay informed about how we are protecting the personally identifiable information we collect. If you continue to use our Services after we post an update to this Privacy Policy, this will indicate your acceptance of the update. 

Last updated Dec 1, 2016
